I'm a comedian this is a good job I also
I'm also a filmmaker sort of an amateur
filmmaker I'm filming a horror movie
right now I'm shooting it exclusively
using the backup camera in my
Subaru I shoot mostly in the Walmart
parking
lot those people are an edge and they
get scared real
easy I love my backup camera do you guys
have a backup camera in your car some of
you guys I it spoiled me cuz now when I
get into rental like I have now it has
no camera in I'm like what you want me
to turn all the way
around what am I an
owl that camera got me in trouble though
a little while ago I was on a camping
trip on the way to camping trip and the
cop pulled me out I was speeding and the
cop comes and takes my license and stuff
and he takes it back to the car he was
taking a long time and I couldn't see
him because of my camping gear I don't
want to see what was going on back there
so I turned my car on put the car in
Reverse so I could see the backup camera
not a good
move between my backup camera and his
front-facing camera we got good footage
of my
beating